<resources>
    <string name="app_name">BioTowerDefense</string>

    <string name="dummy_button">Dummy Button</string>
    <string name="dummy_content">DUMMY\nCONTENT</string>
    <string name="title_activity_store_inventory">StoreInventoryActivity</string>
    <string name="tab_text_inventory">Inventory</string>
    <string name="tab_text_store">Store</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="startGame">Start</string>
    <string name="pauseGame">Pause</string>
    <string name="title_activity_library">LibraryActivity</string>

    <string name="penicillin_description">Penicillin (PCN or pen) antibiotics were among the first
        medications to be effective against many bacterial infections caused by staphylococci and
        streptococci. Penicillins are still widely used today, though many types of bacteria have
        developed resistance following extensive use.  Penicillin was discovered in 1928 by Scottish
        scientist Alexander Fleming.  Penicillin targets the cell wall of bacteria.</string>

    <string name="vancomycin_description">Vancomycin is an antibiotic used to treat a number of
        bacterial infections.  It is recommended intravenously as a treatment for complicated skin
        infections, bloodstream infections, and meningitis caused by Staphylococcus aureus.
        Vancomycin targets the cell wall of bacteria.</string>

    <string name="linezolid_description">Linezolid is an antibiotic used for the treatment of
        infections caused by Gram-positive bacteria that are resistant to other antibiotics.
        Linezolid is active against most Gram-positive bacteria that cause disease, including
        streptococci, vancomycin-resistant enterococci (VRE), and methicillin-resistant
        Staphylococcus aureus (MRSA).  Linezolid targets the ribosome of bacteria.</string>

    <string name="staph_description">Staphylococcus aureus is among the most common hospital
        acquired pathogens. It is a normal inhabitant of the skin and mucous membranes in the
        nose of a healthy human.  Approximately 30% of the normal healthy population is affected
        by S. aureus as it asymptomatically colonizes on the skin of human hosts. Though some host
        colonization can be benign, a puncture or break in the skin can prompt this bacterium to
        enter a wound and cause infections. The best preventive measure is simply regular hand
        washing.  S. aureus is the most common cause of staph infections and is responsible for
        various diseases including: mild skin infections (impetigo, folliculitis, etc.), invasive
        diseases (wound infections, osteomyelitis, bacteremia with metastatic complications, etc.),
        and toxin mediated diseases (food poisoning, toxic shock syndrome or TSS, scaled skin
        syndrome, etc.).  MRSA: The first serious emergence of antibiotic resistance staph occurred
        with a specific strain we refer to as Methicillin-Resistant Staphylococcus aureus,
        abbreviated as MRSA. This strain expressed a modified penicillin-binding protein and
        is present in 4 forms of Staph.</string>

    <string name="strep_desription">Streptococcus pyogenes, also known as the flesh eating bacteria,
        is the most pathogenic bacterium in the whole genus. The name pyogenes comes from the word
        pyogenic, which is a classification for the streptococci that are associated with pus
        formation. The effects of this microbe range from mild illnesses such as strep throat and
        impetigo to more serious diseases such as scarlet fever, glomerulonephritis, and necrotizing
        fasciitis.  However, if strep throat is untreated, it will lead to rheumatic fever, which is
        pretty rare now in the United States but was a more serious problem before the 20th century.
        S. pyogenes usually begins infection on the surface of the skin or in the throat. From
        there, the bacterium begins to spread into deeper areas of the skin, which can potentially
        lead to life-threatening   Streptococcus pyogenes is an unusually successful pathogen
        because of many different properties. First of all, the organism is able to adhere to the
        cells of its host with strong adhering mechanisms, which is important because the organism
        would be easily removed by mucus or salivary fluid.  Not only does Streptococcus pyogenes
        adhere to its host cells, but it also invades them.  Streptococcus pyogenes affects its
        hosts in many different ways and causes a large range of diseases. The Center for Disease
        Control and Prevention (CDC) reports some symptoms of the diseases caused by Streptococcus
        pyogenes. They range from mild to severe, such as fever, severe pain, dizziness, and red
        rash at wound site. The symptoms at first might not seem severe, but in some cases the
        diseases have caused death to certain individuals.
    </string>

    <string name="pneumonia_description">Klebsiella pneumoniae is a gram negative bacterium. It is
        rod-shaped and measures 2 µm by 0.5 µm. In 1882, Friedlander C. Uber first discovered
        Klebsiella to be a pathogen that caused pneumonia. Many hospital cases around the world
        have been linked to K. pneumoniae. K. pneumoniae is commonly found in the gastrointestinal
        tract and hands of hospital personnel. The reason for its pathogenicity is the thick capsule
        layer surrounding the bacterium.   K. pneumoniae is an important cause of human infections.
        Infections or diseases are usually nosocomial or hospital-acquired. In 1998, K. pneumoniae
        and K. oxytoca accounted for 8% of nosocomial bacterial infections in the United States and
        in Europe. Diseases include urinary tract infections, pneumonia, septicemias, and soft
        tissue infections. The diseases caused by K. pneumoniae can result in death for patients
        who are immunodeficient. Treatment is done by antibiotics such as clinafloxacin. But, there
        are an increasing amount of antibiotic-resistance strains. Ciprofloxacin is an antibiotic
        that is becoming less effective.</string>
</resources>
